Kelly Bruce

Dedicated software engineering student at Epicodus. Eager to apply my 5+ years experience in management and my technical knowledge to creatively solve problems and meet business goals.

PROJECTS - github links underlined for reference

Botanical Adventure MVC and API - C#, CSS, .NET, SQL, Entity, JavaScript

- Used to help user identify plants in the PNW
- API provides a database of mushrooms, trees, and plants

Portland Event Finder - JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Webpack, Jest

 Calls upon the PredictHQ and EventBright APIs to return popular events in Portland, Oregon

RecipeBox - C#, CSS, .NET, SQL

- Allows the user to create an account to track and rank recipes
- Allows the user to search for recipe by category/tag

Currency Exchange - JavaScript, Jest, HTML, Webpack, Node

 Displays conversions of currencies between USD and other select currencies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Morrison Child and Family Services

Portland, OR - Administrative Coordinator March 2021 - June 2022

- Provided a high level of customer service to clients using active listening and problem solving for behaviorally challenged clients
- Maintained electronic health records for 4 outpatient clinics
- Supported scheduling needs for 4 outpatient clinics, triage, and medication services

Holiday Inn Portland Airport

Portland, OR — Event Sales Manager December 2018 - October 2020

- Negotiated and secured contracts for over 30,000 sq. ft. event space
- Generated over \$100,000 in contracted revenues that exceeded yearly business goals
- Designed marketing materials for solicitation
- Maintained flawless communication between internal departments and clients
- Fostered relationships with clients to encourage repeat business
- Delivered smooth execution of events that required catering services, rooms, and audio visual equipment

EDUCATION

Web & Mobile Development - Epicodus

August 2022 - present

- C#/React
- 27 weeks
- 60+ projects
- C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Pair Programming

Nonprofit Fund Development -Mendoza College of Business

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- C#/.NET
- HTML/CSS
- SQL
- MVC
- Object Oriented
- Test Driven Development
- Webpack
- Pair Programming
- Sales/Marketing
- CRM Management

VOLUNTEER

Office Moms and Dads Fundraising Committee Vancouver, WA

Ronald McDonald House Tucson, Arizona